ON BODY AND SOUL
You should come down...
You'll see it can't be repaired.
You never come down!
You haven't been down in years.
It's not your business,
but you are the boss...
Keep a woman on a short leash
so she knows her place.
You know what I mean. I'm no brute.
But you need structure...
Could you pick the kids up today?
I want to go out with the girls.
You want to sit with us?
I'm eating with the girls.
Don't forget to get them, okay?
Who's that?
What? Who?
That woman you hired today.
Why wasn't she sent to my office?
Oh, she's not an employee.
She's the new quality inspector.
Bori's on maternity leave.
She's already due?
No, she's taking 2 months off
before the baby's born.
So we've got this woman now.
I'm not too happy about it.
Why?
She's pretty stiff.
We might have problems with her.
She talks like the slaughterhouse
came out of her shiny ass.
Maybe she's just shy.
First day and all...
Maybe...
See? Just what I was talking about.
I'll check it out.
Don't dare to call her Marika!
I made that mistake.
Bon appétit.
I'm Endre, the financial director.
Mária Rácz, quality inspector.
I see, you choose the garden sorrel too.
It's the only good food here.
Not much else though...
Except the shredded squash, maybe.
I always have pottage here if I can.
You know why?
Perhaps because your arm is crippled.
It's easier to eat mash with one hand.
Look, Marika...
May I call you Marika?
Your friend surely mentioned... that I
find it unpleasant to be called that.
Really? No. He didn't.
Then I was wrong. Pardon me.
I find it unpleasant.
Sorry!
Two?
Yes.
How much, Laci?
Thanks.
Bon appétit! I'm Endre,
the financial director.
Mária Rácz, quality inspector.
She seems to be lonely...
that's why I came over here.
I'm a bit scared. I don't
know what he wants.
She must be nervous.
I'll pick an ordinary topic.
I see, you chose the garden sorrel too.
It's the only good food here.
And shredded squash.
And the shredded squash, maybe.
Not much else though.
I should answer something now...
and then we'd be conversing already.
Hey!
Don't walk all over it!
OK, OK, sorry.
I'll get your coffee right away.
I'm making yours in a sec!
You're in no hurry, right?
Here you go.
And he says it's not overtime!
Why on earth not?
Look at her huddled alone in the dark...
Should we ask her to join us?
Their kind has coffee upstairs.
Bori always had her coffee with us.
That was Bori.
Well, I'm asking her anyway.
Hello, doctor!
Hi, guys.
I don't add salt, to keep it soft.
Only after.
Józsi, this is Grade B?
Fuckin' yes...
I can't believe it!
I work out.
Three times a week.
There won't be a problem with my strength.
People always say... I should do
something with my excess energy.
I'm not aggressive or anything...
What else can I tell you?
After my training I worked at...
I'd like to ask you something, young man.
What's your name again?
Sándor Markó.
Sándor, what do you think
about these animals...
that we process here... so to say.
I don't think anything.
What should I think?
Don't you feel sorry for them?
Not me. Bam!
I see...
Is there a problem?
Blood never bothered me.
Look, if you don't feel sorry for them...
that's not going to work here.
You can't work here like that.
So it was a trick question, right?
If I say I feel sorry
for them, I'm neurotic.
You'll have a breakdown.
Find some other job.
So you're not hiring me? Is that it?
Hello?
This new chick is labeling
everything Grade B!
These nice cattle!
- I see.
- Should I talk to her?
No, don't do anything!
I'll go down and talk to her.
I'm not the HR manager.
You're already hired.
It was just friendly advice.
It certainly is cold here.
So, how do you like working with us?
Thank you, everything is fine.
I won't beat around the bush.
Look, the girls said...
you're labeling everything Grade B.
The cattle seemed quite nice.
Don't you think?
I do.
Then what was the problem?
They were fattier than regulation.
Much fattier?
No. About 2-3 millimeters on average.
You've got hawk eyes. 2 millimeters...
Yes, I have good eyes. I know.
And that makes them all Grade B?
That's what's in the regulations.
The regulations.
Oh, right.
Yes, they are my guidelines.
What's going on?
Did hell break loose down there again?
Yes, two bulls need fast sedation!
The paper from the doc?
I'll give it to you later on.
OK, but don't forget cause
they'll kick my ass!
Sure.
I'll have it sent up at
the end of the shift.
Isn't she at her station?
Second day and she's already no show?
No, she's there.
Sitting motionless... like this.
Makes you feel real creepy.
Then where's the paper?
She started to fuss about.
I got the fuck out of there.
Here. But I didn't hear any of this.
Got it?
Where'd they find this woman?
Who knows?
I invited her upstairs
for coffee yesterday.
And?
You don't see her anywhere, do you?
Well, Snow White has arrived.
Look, they froze up totally.
I go to the hairdresser's today.
Can you pick up the kids?
Sure...
And we need groceries.
You can do both at once.
Buy some pudding, for sure.
- The powdered stuff?
- Yeah.
And bread, milk, bologna...
Write a list.
OK.
Oh, and we got a new quality inspector.
Maria something-or-other...
Yes, that's her.
You don't say.
She is precise as hell...
No, whoever you send us is fine.
Okay, I'll tell her.
We've got a problem.
We have to hire two people
for the night shift.
Looks like we've got
a new cock in the henhouse.
You were a pole dancer...
Look...
He's met his match.
I've come from the robotics department.
So the good doctor will...
stamp me.
He's making a fool of her!
So what?
What's going on here?
The cops are here.
I can see that. So?
I dunno... but I can only let employees in.
Go upstairs, they're interviewing everyone.
What did Pista say?
The cops are here.
Who are they after?
How should I know?
This is very awkward...
I have no idea who it might be.
Not even a wild guess!
The cabinet was locked, as always.
There's nothing more I can say.
There's no point. It's full of prints.
István, get the lady to the office.
This way, please.
Relax, it'll be fine.
You got a tissue?
No.
Sorry about this...
He's never been to a slaughterhouse before.
Yes, one has to get used to it.
Here's everyone who has access...
to the medicine cabinet.
One of them is me.
It could have been one of us.
What is this mating powder, anyway?
Is it really that strong?
It's strong, and works fast, too.
A mating is done in 3 minutes.
It's not so funny for us.
I hope we can settle this quietly.
A story like this? No way.
That 50th class reunion, for example!
Yes, it really does get
your instincts going.
But jumping at each other
like crazed animals?
It was developed for cattle.
A bull weighs in around 400 kilos.
Boss? Where should I...?
A speedy result would be nice.
We don't want this to happen again.
Are you feeling better?
Uh-huh, thank you, yes.
Do you have here mental hygiene screenings?
Sure, every year. The
next one is in 2 months.
Great.
Has anyone's behavior changed recently?
I mean, anyone acting weird? Unhinged?
It's hard to tell from
up here in the office.
Listen, run the annual screening now.
Let me recommend someone.
She's worked for us in the past.
OK, but... who'll pay for the psychologist?
Us, or...?
Well, it's worth the price, right?
The steak is in the striped bag.
Well, are they satisfactory?
Pardon me.
Date of first seminal emission?
Excuse me?
Ejaculation.
I'm sure you remember.
Pardon me for my... staring before.
No problem.
It happens...
Well?
Is this really a question?
Look, these are regulation questions.
This is how you started
with the butcher boys?
The question order is not set...
Uh-huh.
But yes, I asked them all
and they all answered.
That must have been a real experience.
I see you're embarrassed...
I'm not embarrassed!
Relax. There's nothing personal
in this question.
It happens to all boys, no?
Come on. Try and remember.
Alright. I was 10. Next question?
10...?
It's a bit early.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Fine...
Tell me what you dreamt last night.
It wasn't anything special.
Yes?
I dreamt that I was a deer.
I don't know what you'll conclude
from that. Probably nothing.
So you were a deer. And?
That's about it.
I did things deer usually do, I suppose.
Like what?
I wandered around in the woods.
Drank from a stream. Stuff like that.
Were you alone?
No.
I was with... there was another deer.
Was it another stag? Or a doe?
A doe.
Are you certain or just assuming?
I know.
How? Did you mate?
My dear lady, I have to disappoint.
We did not mate.
We wandered the woods, looked for grass.
But only found a few juicy leaves.
We had to dig them out from under the snow.
We went down to the stream, to drink.
Our noses touched when we drank.
That's all.
I didn't mount her, I didn't fuck her.
And I don't want to mount you either.
I just looked at you,
like any normal man would.
Again, I apologize if I was insolent...
but I'd like to start the real work now.
Of course. Sure.
Your intense reaction is very interesting.
Do you perhaps have any erection problems?
Is this part of the questionnaire?
Your response was so
heated it seems logical...
You said you ask everyone
the same questions.
May I ask you to adhere to this?
Sure, sure...
When did you lose your virginity?
C'mon, tell me what they asked.
I dunno. A bunch of nonsense.
What's my favorite food...
or if I get dizzy spells...
She also asked me what I dreamt.
I'm not telling her that, for sure.
I'll say I don't remember.
She can't read anything into it.
They know if you're lying. That's how
the questions are put together...
And what's the woman like?
She's got tits like this!
So what did you dream, honey?
I'm not telling.
- No.
- Oh, come on.
OK.
I dreamt...
I was sitting on a light-blue horse...
Ha ha, really funny. Whatever, forget it.
Too bad, it was nice.
Tell us what you dream, Zsóka.
You don't want to know that, honey.
I just made a fool of myself for telling.
What do you do in your dreams?
Me?
I fuck.
So... time of first menstruation?
November 5, 1998.
Any surgery?
None.
Contagious illnesses?
Chicken pox.
When?
March 21 - April 7, 1990.
You remember so precisely?
I remembered.
I see.
It's rather unusual.
Is there some reason for it?
No.
OK. Tell we what you dreamt last night.
You don't remember?
I do.
I'm just thinking of how to tell it.
I'll finish in a moment.
Sure, fine.
Please.
Yes?
It would be easier without this noise.
What noise?
Oh...
Sorry. It wasn't nice of me.
I've had a long day.
But I'm really listening now.
Tell me your dream.
I was very hungry.
I rooted through the snow...
but there was no food anywhere.
My companion helped me search.
He found a thick, juicy
leaf under the snow.
He let me have all of it. I ate it.
It didn't taste bad...
just a bit nauseating.
Afterwards, I felt strange.
Were you an animal in your dream?
Yes.
What animal? Can you tell me?
A deer.
Go on. What else happened?
We went down to the stream.
Your companion...
Well...
did you mate?
Why don't you answer?
I was just waiting for you...
to find what you were looking for.
Did you find it?
Yes, I found it. Thank you.
So then?
No.
No, what?
We didn't mate.
Oh, right.
But was there physical contact?
His nose touched mine.
Our noses touched when we drank.
Tell me, why you're doing this to me?
What, doctor?
As you wish. Send the next person in.
Oooh, they called you back in?
Don't worry, I'm sure it's nothing.
Relax.
Stop touching me...
Leave me alone. There's no problem.
OK, forget I said anything...
I want to know about your
little private joke.
You think it's funny?
I need to evaluate the material.
And the dream analysis is a part of it. OK?
Yes.
Then tell me what you
really dreamt last night!
Not what the two of you arranged.
I'm just trying to do my job.
I don't care about anyone's private life.
I want to go home, take a shower.
That's all.
Doctor, maybe you've overworked yourself?
It happens.
Alright...
I dreamt that I was a deer.
I don't know what you'll conclude
from that. Probably nothing.
So you were a deer. And?
That's about it.
I did things deer usually do, I suppose...
What an odd coincidence, right?
Anyway, I just wanted to say...
we don't have to feel awkward.
We're adults after all, right?
Yes.
Actually, it's kind of funny, no?
It's funny.
Bon appétit.
How's the meat?
The meat is satisfactory.
I always end up with leathery meat here...
What did you dream last night?
I didn't dream anything.
Ah...
Too bad...
Then I'd better go sit elsewhere.
I prefer eating alone.
May I?
Don't think I consider you a leper too.
Did they find out who did it?
No.
Well, I've got a tip.
Leave me alone.
Personally, I don't think it's you.
We'll see what that shrink
lady comes up with.
She's a silly goose.
She really messed with my mind.
I'd bang her though.
Don't you even want to know who I suspect?
Tell me, I know you want to.
Well...
I think it's obvious.
That guy Sándor...
I don't think he's got all his marbles.
The way he's all over the women...
And the mating powder and all...
You see? He's a sex maniac.
What do you think?
Isn't it logical?
Yeah, it's a good idea.
Cause if you think so too,
we might want to tell the cops, no?
Could you return my tray?
You're the one in contact with them...
Well, in my dream, I was a deer again...
Like every night, for a while now.
Aaand...
There was this doe.
Where?
Well, in a forest. Where else?
Actually...
It really was kind of a strange place.
Beside a small, round pond.
I've never seen such a small pond before.
I mean, in real life.
How about you?
What nice things did you dream?
This.
What?
The same as you.
You're just saying that.
No.
I don't believe you.
That's okay...
I wrote it down.
Oh, sorry...
Well
See you tonight then.
Tell me...
Why did you run away?
I looked for you at the lake too.
Are you angry?
Hello, doctor.
You look really hot today.
Looks like the boss thinks so too.
Excuse me. Just a professional question...
I bet your legs are...
Coffee?
May I come in just this once?
No, you may not.
Come on...
You know that regulations forbid that...
We'll just have our coffee... and I'm gone.
Is that alright?
I just want to discuss something with you.
You shouldn't take that
guy Sándor seriously.
Okay.
Men sometimes talk a load of nonsense.
What did he say to you?
Never mind. It's not important.
Here is my phone number.
And I will enter yours.
I don't have one.
I didn't mean to impose.
I really didn't mean to impose.
That's not how I am.
And what did you say?
That I have no phone.
Uh-huh.
So what's it supposed to mean?
What do you think?
Perhaps he didn't believe
me for some reason.
Very good.
And could you explain why?
Maybe I used the wrong tone of voice.
Or I forgot to make eye contact.
No, I made eye contact, I remember.
His pupils contracted.
Look, these days, everyone
has a cell phone.
Maybe that was the reason.
It's strange to talk to you like this.
Yes, Marika...
You're a real, grownup woman.
It's strange for me too.
Maybe I could give you the number of...
a colleague who works with adults.
Or simply buy yourself a phone.
Hello.
You came down early today.
Bon appétit.
I'm buying a phone tomorrow.
You have a phone...
You just think I'm old
and my arm is crippled.
It makes me feel bad.
I think you are beautiful.
I don't believe you.
You can see in 3 signs, if someone's lying.
Shall I teach you too?
OK.
Number one: The pupils.
If the pupils dilate...
Pupils dilate according to light changes...
don't try and make a fool of me.
I know why you're angry with me.
I'm not angry.
Today I went to...
Someone explained to me...
I don't care what you discussed about me.
You probably laughed at me.
He said you are angry with me
because you're jealous.
Is it true? Are you really jealous?
Yes.
I think you fancy that worker, that Sándor.
You're mistaken.
Come on!
You're wrong. I'm afraid of him.
Is that... true?
Yes.
Then everything's alright again, right?
I'm totally stressed.
Why?
Uhh, forget it.
Uh-huh.
Listen...
Back in the day, did you screw my wife?
Christ.
So you did.
I know she's slept with half the factory.
Sándor's on the agenda now.
Oh, come on.
I'm not a complete idiot.
Whatever.
We worked through this already.
You got an aspirin?
Hello.
You came down early today.
It's 1:30.
I didn't come early.
I'm buying a phone tomorrow.
Then buy one.
I think you are beautiful.
I can't believe this.
What's going on? Did you hook up?
Are you crazy?
Why exactly do you have...
mating powder at a slaughterhouse?
Well, it's not really legal...
but not illegal either.
Sometimes we help with mating...
private deals, no papers.
But it's not a whole lot of money.
It's not making us rich or anything.
You can report it if you want.
No way.
Don't worry...
I just couldn't fit the pieces together.
The meat was really yummy...
Béla...
The usual.
Hey, boss!
What did the cop want?
What are you doing out here?
Oh, you're my dad now? It's nice.
Return to work. Don't make me say it again.
What'll happen if you say it again?
Are you gonna beat me up?
Quit this job, son...
before you get into real trouble.
What are you talking about?
I know you did it.
You despise me from the start.
You're right. Smart boy.
Dad, I don't ask you that often!
That's not what I said.
What do you spend on besides smokes?
You never even have a
crust of bread at home.
I stopped smoking 4 years ago.
All the more, then.
Listen, kid, that's my business.
Look, the situation is this...
Will you get it?
Yes? Hello?
I bought a phone.
Is this a bad time?
No, it's fine.
Would you call me tonight?
We could fall asleep together.
Well, that's a great idea.
It really is.
Tonight, then.
Who was that?
A colleague. You don't know her.
Hello?
Yes.
Good evening.
Well, I'm going to bed now.
Alright then.
I've already taken my sleeping pill.
I usually fall asleep pretty quickly.
Look, one more thing...
Er...
You don't have to be afraid of me. I...
Sorry, forget it...
I know I'm a little ridiculous.
Sleep well.
It was lovely.
We could go out for lunch tomorrow.
Let me invite you to my old favorite place.
Hello.
Well, did you find anything?
Just one person, but,
you know... it's not actual proof of crime.
Who is it?
Jenő Vári...
The HR manager.
Are you surprised?
Are you 100% sure?
In my profession, you can't ever
really say... you're 100% sure.
But... it's a very strong probability.
Here is my report.
Shall I forward them to the police?
No need. We'll do it.
Did you give us your invoice?
Yes, yes, sure.
Thank you for coming in personally.
Good-bye.
Just out of professional curiosity...
Your colleague's dream...
Did a similar coincidence
ever happen again?
I suppose you compared dreams since then...
No. We didn't compare.
Good-bye.
So it really was a joke?
You arranged it beforehand?
Yes, that's exactly what happened.
I'm sorry, it was a childish idea.
I apologize.
Good-bye.
Well...
what did the great shrink come up with?
Nothing much.
How come?
She thinks it was Sándor too.
Seriously?
So what now?
Do we fire him?
What do you think?
Will you tell the cops?
I suppose.
I'll call them tomorrow.
Right, of course.
These tests... They don't mean much.
It was stupid to do it in the first place.
Whose idea was it anyway?
I think it was mine.
Oh... sorry.
It wasn't Sándor.
No?
I know it wasn't him.
Really?
It was me.
I don't know what got into me.
I just got fed up.
Yeah, it happens.
Sometimes you just get fed up.
So...
What now?
Nothing. Don't do it again.
But...
No one got hurt.
They just had a weird night, that's all.
The police will close
the case after a while.
They're not too concerned about it anyway.
It was nasty of me to blame it on Sándor.
Yes.
But you know...
It was.
Sándor!
I want to apologize to you.
So... I apologize.
And we can be on a first-name basis.
Thank you.
I mean, thanks.
We could have a beer together...
No, I'm in no hurry. I'm free all evening.
You want to hook yourself a man, doctor?
Yes.
That's not how you do it.
How do I do it?
You're nice and tall.
You should wear clothes that show it.
Don't dress like a waif.
Turn around.
Nice ass too...
I've never noticed it before.
Stand up straight.
There!
That's worth more than any fancy clothes.
But the way you hold your head...
Chin up.
Not that much...
Then you'll seem cocky.
That's what they say about you anyway...
Movement...
People underestimate...
the power of movement, honey.
The effect of how you move.
Look...
You don't need much.
Too much ruins everything.
Now...
Walk along here. Show me.
Chips.
Tissues.
Two?
Sure.
Listen, do you have any proper aftershave?
I do.
Thanks...
Strange...
This place was always full.
Hello?
Hi.
The food here is great.
Lunch?
Yes, if it's not an inconvenience for you.
What do you mean?
Forget it.
Never mind...
Tell me...
Does János still work here?
So you wanna have lunch or just chat?
I have an idea.
I'd really love to sleep with you.
Oh...
Nothing else.
Just sleep in the same room.
Fall asleep together.
And when we wake up...
we can talk about what we dreamt.
What do you say?
I can't sleep right now.
Me neither.
What should we do?
I'd better go home.
Stay.
Let's talk.
Okay.
About what?
Well...
Or, let's play cards!
I don't know how to play.
I'll teach you.
And ten.
I call.
Sixteen.
Incredible!
How are you so good at this?
Honestly now.
Did you know I was bluffing?
I thought you were.
But how?
You couldn't read my face, for sure.
I was so careful.
I didn't move my face at all.
Exactly! You didn't twitch at all.
Oh.
But how did you know what I had?
I remembered the cards.
My memory is abnormally developed.
It has its downsides too.
You simply remember everything?
Your first sentence to
me was: "Bon appétit."
That's not so hard to remember.
Then we introduced ourselves...
I remember it too.
Your fifth sentence was:
You chose the garden sorrel too.
Not much else though...
except the shredded squash, maybe.
God, that's incredible.
What about, say...
the 17th sentence?
I won't beat around the bush.
Look, the girls said...
you're labeling everything Grade B.
The cattle seemed quite nice.
Don't you think?
Good God...
that's uncanny.
But are you sure that was the 17th?
Shall I start from the beginning?
I believe you.
Did I misunderstand something?
You know...
I closed this chapter of my life
a few years ago.
There were women...
thinking back now,
fewer would have been better.
Then when...
There was a point when I said...
that's it.
I'm out of the game.
And I was fine with that, till now.
And now...
Do you think it's so easy...
making a fool of myself now?
Will you get the kids from school?
I have to go to the hairdresser's.
Sure.
Then you can buy groceries...
Are you sure... you don't want to talk
to an adult therapist?
I am.
Look...
I don't know what to say.
This is just like anything else.
Observation. Practice.
I'm doing it.
I watch 3 different series...
and porno movies...
I don't recommend that.
It's physical contact...
that causes you problems, right?
Yes.
Well, then practice that.
Do you have a pet?
No.
That's alright...
I don't really know what to say.
Try this, for instance...
close your eyes...
put your hand on your face...
and caress it gently.
Like this.
Try to touch all sorts of...
Is it possible... that two people
dream the same thing?
I mean, that they meet in their dreams?
What made you think of this now?
Can it happen?
Look, you're a smart woman...
You're a university graduate.
I don't understand this at all.
Another thing that might help...
is music.
It can also have a mood-altering effect.
I'd like to listen to these.
Won't that be a bit too many?
No.
Do it. You've got time.
Sorry, we're closing.
We're closing!
You want one of them?
I don't know.
What are you looking for?
Love music.
What???
Music for people in love.
And you didn't like any of these?
Listen...
I show you my favorite if you want.
Will you listen to it?
No, I'll buy it.
"Forgive me, Hera, I cannot stay."
"He cut out my tongue,
there is nothing to say."
"Love me, oh Lord, he threw me away."
"He laughed at my sins,
in his arms I must stay."
"He wrote,"
"I am broke, please send for me."
"But I am broken too, and spoken for,"
Damn it...
For fuck's sake already!
The boss...
That wasn't so bad, right?
I don't know why we ever stopped.
Don't miss your last bus.
I'm staying over now.
We'll have a good sleep.
Don't be silly.
What's your problem?
You can't sleep here.
Why not? I don't get you.
I can only sleep alone.
Since when?
Really. I'm serious.
You can fuck me, but you
can't sleep beside me?
Don't be stupid.
Are you crazy?
Well, you're certainly not kicking me out
in the middle of the night.
It's only after 11.
Stop it already. Don't make me mad.
Good night.
I have no idea what to eat.
The ratatouille was pretty good yesterday.
I'll have salad for sure.
Hello.
I could sleep over tonight.
I brought my pajamas with me.
Look...
I've been meaning to tell you...
I don't want to hurt you...
But there's not much point in doing this.
Right?
A risotto please.
I thought it over last night.
We're just not cut out for this.
It just wasn't working out.
What would you like?
Cream of celery or potato soup?
Celery.
At least we tried. It's no tragedy.
We can still be good friends.
Of course.
Actually, it'll be easier this way.
No more tension, right?
Right.
Bye, then...
Forgive me, Hera, I cannot stay.
"He cut out my tongue,
there is nothing to say."
"Love me, oh Lord, he threw me away."
"He laughed at my sins,
in his arms I must stay."
"He wrote,"
"I am broke, please send for me."
"But I am broken too,
and spoken for, do not tempt me."
"Her skin is white, and I'm..."
Hello?
Good evening.
I don't really have any reason for calling.
Am I bothering you?
No.
And are you having a pleasant evening?
I was listening to music.
But something's wrong with the player.
I'm afraid it's broken.
I didn't even know you liked music.
Actually, I don't.
Just this one song.
But now I can't even
listen to that anymore.
Too bad.
Well, yes.
Alright then...
Bye. Have a nice evening.
You have a nice evening too.
Sorry...
Hello? Are you still there?
Yes, I'm here.
I...
I feel like I'm going to die...
I love you so much.
I love you so much too.
I'd like to...
look into...
Can we meet?
Yes.
I'll hurry.
There's still something I need to do.
It'll take a little while...
but I'll really hurry.
We need to keep you in for a few days.
The psychologist will
come to see you tomorrow.
The nurse will show your bed.
I'm sleepy.
Let's sleep then.
Will you slice the tomato for me?
Sorry.
Here.
Would you like some cold cuts?
No, thank you.
By the way, what did we dream last night?
Somehow I can't remember.
I think I didn't dream anything.
"Forgive me, Hera, I cannot stay."
"He cut out my tongue,
there is nothing to say."
"Love me, oh Lord, he threw me away."
"He laughed at my sins,
in his arms I must stay."
"He wrote,"
"I am broke, please send for me."
"But I am broken too,
and spoken for, do not tempt me."
"Her skin is white, and
I'm light as the sun,"
"so holy light shines on
the things you have done."
"So I asked him how he became this man,"
"how did he learn to hold
fruit in his hands,"
"and where is the lamb
that gave you your name,"
"he had to leave though
I begged him to stay"
"Left me alone when I needed the light,"
"fell to my knees and I wept for my life."
"if he had of stayed you might understand,"
"if he had of stayed you never
would have taken my hand."
"He wrote, oh love, please send for me,"
"but I am broken too,
and spoken for, do not tempt me."
"And where is the lamb
that gave you your name,"
"He had to leave though
I begged him to stay."
"Begged him to stay in
my cold wooden grip,"
"begged him to stay by
the light of this ship."
"Me fighting him, fighting
like fighting dawn,"
"and the waves came and stole him
and took him to war."
"He wrote, I'm broke,
please send for me."
"But I'm broken too,
and spoken for, do not tempt me."
"Forgive me, Hera, I cannot stay,"
"cut out my tongue, there
is nothing to say."
"Love me, oh Lord, he threw me away,"
"he laughed at my sins,
in his arms I must say."
"We write, that's alright,
I miss his smell."
"We speak when spoken to,
and that suits us well"
"During the shooting of our film
animals were harmed,"
"but none of them for
the sake of this film."
"We just documented the daily
routine of a slaughterhouse."
"That suits us well.
That suits me well."